{
    "id": "2a29c49a70904e6c94ffcdbeeafdf945",
    "title": "More And More Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I need ……………….. time to finish this job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00d78c701454434c8e8dc2b7aac7fbc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could I have some ………………… potatoes?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6b3f5a160bf4c5b8a4aa13c13f9d85b"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... students are having to borrow money these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "More",
                "More of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "57ceb184dc9a4f9fb2f20ad288946563"
        },
        {
            "question": "Two hundred years ago, much ……………… India was covered with trees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81ffe2751ca54dd1bd70e0d1b08d07b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ..................... a fool than I thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c184abca9fa4be08343dce62f1b1a0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Three ………………….. the hostages have been rescued.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d022b9f94cf14038b84cac83b7067459"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could I have some …………………. that fried rice?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "652ee4f7607e41e28fe146de3951adb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think any ………………… them are interested.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f65ea5efa9243568ff18394bbe4a674"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is just one ………………….. hurdle to cross.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35b4f79b2cec4941913f8d9cc62f411d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate this city ……………….. every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2528bce89931498b97bd83592488523e"
        }
    ]
}